question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "History",
     "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
                                       "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
                                      "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Type 1 diabetes is a result of the liver working improperly.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Vehicles",
                                      "question": "The majority of Subaru vehicles are made in China.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
     "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
